[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Desire For A Child",
        "Description": "Primrose has asked you to find her darling daughter, Hazel. Your search starts at her childhood home in Hakenstadt.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where would she most likely go?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hakenstadt. It's where Hazel grew up, where she said \"mama\" for the first time. Have you ever experienced a child's first word? It's utterly delightful! \\n\\nPlease, find my baby girl and bring her back to me.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Any word on my Hazel? She's a tall, smiling brunette with dancing eyes. \\n\\nAlways happy, no matter what challenge comes her way.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What did you find in Hakenstadt? I miss that place. \\n\\nMy husband and I taught Hazel to sew there. She loved making little dresses for her dolls.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Truth Behind Transmutations",
        "Description": "Hazel has been experimenting with forbidden life magic. Continue your search further east in Krummholm.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why would Hazel want a child?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My poor girl! I knew she longed to experience motherhood. I'd speak often of the joy I felt carrying her, feeling her grow inside me. \\n\\nSeeing her excitement as she experienced this mysterious new world was an indescribable joy.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Any news on my Hazel? I've been worried sick. \\n\\nI couldn't bear losing her as well. She's the sunshine of my soul.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You're back! What news of Hazel? \\n\\nWait. What do you mean she wasn't at Krummholm?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Hope Of The Living",
        "Description": "Primrose fears what her daughter may have done. Find Hazel and bring her safely back home.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She was clearly affected by your stories.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I only sought to comfort her. And she knows this island can be cruel. I love my Hazel, the woman she's become. She's brave and beautiful. \\n\\nPlease find her. Say her mother misses her terribly.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Please find Hazel and tell her to come back home. \\n\\nTell her the two of us are enough. We have to be.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "No! Hazel! Why did you do this to yourself? This is my fault… I drove her to this… \\n\\nI'm sorry, you did all you could, stranger. Leave this old woman to her tears...",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Starting the Fire",
        "Description": "Gather strange torches from Richmire region and bring them to Torchy Cabrera in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What is it that they say?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ah well, if you have not heard anything, then perhaps it is best we keep it that way.\\n\\nSuffice to say that I am no longer welcome in the Restless Shore settlement. It's really because of my research.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be on the lookout for the strange, ghostly torches. And try not to get burned too badly.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, yes. Don't you see? The light, the color… it is truly beautiful. \\n\\nI will study these and see if I might discover how they burn so long and so bright.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Burning from the Inside",
        "Description": "Collect Perpetual Illumination Essences from Ancients at Aqua Acadia and bring them to Torchy Cabrera in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Depends. What's the favor?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I believe the Ancients knew the secrets of Eternal Fire and Eternal Light as well. \\n\\nHave you ever noticed the perpetual glow that clings to the walking corpses of the Ancient Guardians?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Amid the ruins of Aqua Acadia to the north, you will see for yourself. \\n\\nThe Guardians there glow more than anywhere else. Gather their essence, my friend.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Perfect… perfect! This illumination essence is the missing link! \\n\\nCombined with the substance in the torches from Karburg, I feel certain we have found the secret!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "WaterT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Hellfire \u0026amp; Brimstone Oven",
        "Description": "Travel to Navarro's Kitchen and defeat Chef Navarro and collect \"Navarro's Flaming Duck Recipe\". Then bring it to Torchy in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you mean by that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You must help me clear my name so I can go home. You see, I was exiled from the settlement for starting a fire… \\n\\nBut for once, it was NOT me who ignited the flame. I was framed, you see!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Chef Navarro's Kitchen is not far, and I feel certain he still carries his \"Flaming Duck Recipe.\" \\n\\nDefeat the bastard and get the recipe and I can finally clear my name.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "He still had it, didn't he? Yes… yes! This proves that HE was the one who started the fire! \\n\\nThank you, my friend! I cannot thank you enough for helping me get back home.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Denying The Denier",
        "Description": "Travel to Periville, slay the Denier, and bring proof of its demise to Evelyn Van Heck in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I am afraid I haven’t.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I expected as much. Blast.\\n\\nMy companions and I are shadow hunters. We formed a band called the White Skulls to hunt the Corpse Crone and her many abominations. We were chasing such a monster when my companions and I were slain.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Just so we're clear, I am not responsible if The Denier kills you as well. \\n\\nYou take on this bounty at your own risk. I am content to wait here for my company to return.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "He was once our brother. Alas, this terrible fate so often awaits the Crone's many victims.  \\n\\nHere. Your bounty, as promised.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Keeping the Faith",
        "Description": "Travel to Periville and find Joan and Markus. Report back to Evelyn Van Heck in Weaver's Fen with news of their fate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What do you think happened to them?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, I must assume the worst. Joan and Markus had only recently joined our hunt. It's possible they lacked the fortitude to withstand such a harrowing death. \\n\\nCall me sentimental, but…",
        "InProgressResponse": "Hope for the best, prepare for… well, I would rather not think about that.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I am at a loss for words, traveler. \\n\\nThis emblem was a bond of brotherhood. It is a symbol of our commitment to the hunt.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Well-Earned Respite",
        "Description": "Travel to Karburg, slay Ruiz Velazquez, and bring proof of his demise to Evelyn Van Heck in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Do you want me to find him, too?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You have already risked so much. It pains me to ask for your aid again. \\n\\nFor what's it worth, I know where to find him: at the site of his most grim demise.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I pray I am wrong. I do not think I am, but I must cling to hope. \\n\\nToo much despair and we lose ourselves. Just like they did.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Am I truly all that remains? Ruiz and I had such plans. We intended to hunt terrors in the shadow lands of Durevos. \\n\\nHow cruel is fate, that I should live to see him become a monster like those we fought so hard to destroy?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Gators Gone Wild",
        "Description": "Collect alligator scales from Gators in Weaver's Fen and return them to Hunter Samuel in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What did you have in mind?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A hunt, of course! You and I shall venture forth into the marshes in pursuit of the most ferocious, cunning, and formidable beasts this festering land has to offer! \\n\\nJust as my forebears have done since time immemorial!",
        "InProgressResponse": "I shall make my own way into the stinking bog. \\n\\nYou go on ahead. I suspect you will need the head start, after all.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, you have returned! I was beginning to wonder. Now, let me see your trophies. \\n\\nYes... thick, unblemished, and as hard as anything. These are certifiably the remains of several fine beasts. Well done!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "CoatingBeastT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "No Mere Pigs",
        "Description": "Collect boar tusks from Polder Boars in Weaver's Fen and return them to Hunter Samuel just south of the settlement.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What are we hunting now?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Boars! No ordinary boars, but boars the size of three men! We will not waste our skill on mere pigs! \\n\\nBring me the largest tusks you can find, and we shall compare trophies. They're a plague to this region!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Ah, yes, I shall be along promptly! \\n\\nUh, once I have finished oiling my musket, of course.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The prodigal hunter returns! You truly are a fellow after my own heart. \\n\\nLet us see your fine trophies. Hand them over, I say!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The True Contest",
        "Description": "Collect wolf paws from Mallory Wolves, found north of Fenton's Hamlet, and return them to Hunter Samuel in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Does that mean I won?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "How can you have won if there has been no contest? \\n\\nNay, we shall have to settle this once and for all.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I relish the end of our contest. Go on. I am right behind you!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You are simply not going to believe this. My musket was ready, my boots laced, my satchel patched, and a COURIER found me on the road! There was urgent business in the hamlet to attend to. \\n\\nAlas, I must concede.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Stalk of Shame",
        "Description": "Defeat the Werna Packleader at Dusty Paw Burrow, far to the north and west of Weaver’s Fen Hamlet, and collect a trophy from your kill for Hunter Samuel in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I’m listening.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Do you know what it's like, being saddled with a legacy like mine? Why, if people only knew how incompetent I really am, my family name would be utterly ruined. \\n\\nThat is why I need your help.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will not pretend that this arrangement pleases me, my friend, but I am grateful that you have chosen to take pity on me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, well, there it is. She was enormous, wasn’t she? I, uh, I wish I could have seen it myself. \\n\\nAs promised, here is your bounty. And a tip. Your… continuing discretion is appreciated.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Story of the Stones",
        "Description": "Gather stone samples from rubble in the nearby ruins. Then report back to Architect Na Li in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Really old, probably?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, exactly! These stones have been here as long as anyone can remember. If we can learn how the Ancient architects reinforced these structures, imagine what WE could accomplish!\\n\\nSo, I have a theory!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do you have those stone samples for me? They are vital to my research.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Look at this beautiful basalt you’ve brought me. I wonder where the Ancients sourced it from?\\n\\nNow, let’s see about that aging… huh. Wait…that can’t be right.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Spanning the Ages",
        "Description": "Gather stone samples from rubble at South Vega Bridge. Then report back to Architect Na Li in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How old, exactly?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I need another sample from a newer site to be certain. Master Ting Long once theorized that the bridge that spans the marshes was built in a more recent era. \\n\\nCould you bring me samples from South Vega Bridge for comparison?",
        "InProgressResponse": "I hope to have answers for us soon, my friend. \\n\\nAnd if I am right, then we might see some NEW wonders in Aeternum.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Great, you’re back. Let’s take a look at these new samples you've found.\\n\\nInteresting… these are less weathered, but only just. Fascinating.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Deep Time",
        "Description": "Gather stone samples from rubble at Andrometus. Then report back to Architect Na Li in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Wouldn't that mean the Ancients are also that old?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It does, doesn’t it? So many questions, but we must resist the temptation to draw conclusions. Stone dating is far from an established field of study, after all.\\n\\nRegardless, I am looking toward the future, today.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Let me know when you've got those Andrometus samples. \\n\\nI have some theories about how they accomplished these feats of longevity, but I never draw conclusions without proof.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You and I will be friends, after this. Perhaps I will carve your name into the aqueducts of the future. Or would you prefer a temple? Maybe a stone garden?\\n\\nI am certain I can extract their secrets, thanks to you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_PerfumeAlchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "That Beautiful Stench",
        "Description": "Gather materials in Weaver's Fen and then visit an arcane repository to craft a perfume for Tullius Volusus in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It smells like a swamp.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, precisely! \\n\\nThat scent, it is primal, inescapable. It reaches down through your nose, through your lungs, into your very soul. With every breath, it commands, \"Be awake! Be alive!”",
        "InProgressResponse": "Can the unique fragrance of Weaver’s Fen truly be replicated by human hands? I await your return with bated breath.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hmm, yes… decadent, musky, with a sulfuric accord that resonates right through to the top notes… you’ve captured Weaver's Fen perfectly. \\n\\nYou may be a genius, my friend! Ah, my eyes are watering with emotion!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Misplaced Treasure",
        "Description": "Search chests at North Vega Bridge for a clue to Nora’s whereabouts. Then report back to Leonie Roggeveen in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“{playerName}. Pleased to meet you.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Likewise. I was wondering if you might be able to help me? \\n\\nYou see, Nora and I like to play a little game to pass the time. She hides herself and leaves clues for me to find amongst these relics. Brain teasers, and the like.",
        "InProgressResponse": "This game was much less stressful when it took place in EMPTY ruins, you see. I do hope she's alright.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You’re back! And in one piece! Do you have the clue? It could be a coin, a note, an etching…\\n\\nOh, give it here. The suspense is killing me.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Following Nora",
        "Description": "Search chests at Canopus for a clue to Nora’s whereabouts. Then report back to Leonie Roggeveen in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What’s strange?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Something about the iconography she used… It suggests half of a whole. Aha!\\n\\nShe means to have me combine two clues to find her, but this tells me the second clue is at Canopus. Very clever. Care to help again?",
        "InProgressResponse": "As thrilled as I am, her long absence is truly starting to wear on me. Could you hurry with that clue? \\n\\nIt would put me at ease to finally find her.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Another coin! Wonderful, hand it over, let’s see what she has to say…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AntiquarianSpouse_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Odds in Her Favor",
        "Description": "Follow Nora's trail to Aqua Acadia and search chests for the final clue.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Nice job.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Nora thought she could stump me, did she? Me, the greatest coin collector in Aeternum? \\n\\nCome on, give me a tough one, ha!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Hopefully we near the end of our chase, my friend. Nora can handle herself… right?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I see you found my note. Did Dr. Leonie send you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Nora, Found",
        "Description": "Return to Dr. Leonie Roggeveen in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She seems a little stressed, yes.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yeah, no wonder. When those Guardians appeared, the only two things I could think about were \"I'm going to die\" and \"Leonie will be so worried\".",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll meet you and Leonie back on the road. I'll sneak out while you're distracting them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You’re back! Nora told me everything. I am SO relieved.\\n\\nI’m going to have a talk with her about taking some precautions next time. But this was a fine game, and you were an enormous help. Thank you!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_27",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Nose Knows",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Nice to meet you. I'm {playerName}.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hmm, yes, well. This has been a stimulating conversation, but I must get back to work. \\n\\nWith this news of Corruption spreading southward, I may need to relocate soon.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The phosphorus in these urine samples is elevated…it even glows in the dark. Fascinating. \\n\\nBut will it suffice for the repellant? I need an expert.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, you're back? Do you know much about urine? \\n\\nI can't figure out where I've gone wrong! Not enough sulfur? It certainly smells bad enough already…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
